Although we had Jakhaiyas earlier also
but we did not like its quality at all
and if we had even 1%
doubt about the quality then we would
not have sold that thing further.  But this
time when our new consignment arrived, we liked its
quality very much.  The
fragrance was also quite strong.  So
our staff cleaned it a day before.  I
made packets together
and brought one packet home with me.
Because before delivering the goods to you, we
also try it.  So first of all
I cut the raw potatoes into small cubes.
Then we put oil in the pan
and added our Jakhiya and gave it a nice tempering.
After that I added four Kashmiri chillies
and along with it I also added some asafoetida
and let me tell you that Jakhiya is
not used for tempering in our mountains.  Just
like we
use cumin, you
can also use jakhiya.  Then I
added spices etc. and left my vegetable to cook.
And then some of my parcels also arrived
which I had ordered from Flipkart and
as Michu is growing up, he
observes the things around him very carefully and feels them by touching them, so keeping that in
mind I have
ordered a 7D bedsheet for him so that he can
see and feel different colours, patterns and textures and his
sensory development continues and he
slowly learns to understand the things around him
and as soon as
I took Michu along after laying the bedsheet, he liked it very
much and Kichu also became very
happy and I have ordered many such
bedsheets, if you also want its link then
I have tagged it here.